HDML: HyperText Markup Language 
Double Click/Inspect: Can hack and code inside with the (select element) 
Save offline stuff, you can save and play it for free. You can change and hack the game as well with the inspect hack 
People hack websites, by trying to hack the server
It is easier to hack offline games because just hack the file you saved
All you need is a text file to make your own website
HTML Skeleton: Sublime Text 
Unit of web page 
HTML Anatomy: Start Tag (<tag name) Attribute (ATTR #lowercase, font size)
Responsive design, think of what they are viewing it from 
There are 3 parts in a website HTML skeleton, Banner, Carousel
In the skeleton there is HTML, Head, and Body
W3school shows other HTML tags
CSS is content and decoration
HTML is body 
Front end and Back end are what the viewer can see vs what they need to click to see 
Command C the code to get a design from another website to put in yours 
Div is division (used to divided sections on your website)
Bootstrap has helpful tag codes
Java script for animations
